Alejandro Alonzo

451 S Harvard Blvd Los Angeles, CA 90020 United States (626)-243-6274 alejandro.12w@gmail.com www.alejandroalonzo.com

Fully Work Authorized · No Visa Sponsorship Required

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

With over 2 years of experience in web development, I have worked for different companies around the globe. My concept is never stop to learn that's why I've got a personal interest for continuous learning and self improvement.

Key Skills

- Certified Professional in Web Development
- Web Design
- Front End Development
- **Back End Development**
- MEAN Stack (MongoDB, Express, Angular, Node.js)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Web Developer

Difarmed, Barcelona REMOTE

01/01/2022 - 07/31/2022

Company with more than 20 years of experience in the distribution of medicines throughout Spain and main European countries

Build and maintain the official website of each branch in Spain, France, Italy, Germany, Portugal and the UK.

Web Developer 05/01/2021 - 12/31/2021

Idesoftbon, Barcelona

Top in positioning ranking of software development companies in Barcelona, Spain

Worked with a team of programmers to build a marketing websites and e-commerce platforms for ambitious companies originating from Europe.

ADDITIONAL WORK EXPERIENCE

Parts Manager

10/22/2022 - 10/31/2023

Caliber Collision, Los Angeles

- Manage all vehicle parts that enter and leave the workshop.
- Follow up on credits.
- Search for parts availability.

EDUCATION

Associate Science (AS), Web Development, 02/15/2022

IFP, Barcelona, Spain

Bachelor of Arts (BA), Graphic Design, 05/02/2013

Universidad de El Slavador,

CERTIFICATIONS

- MEAN Stack E-Commerce App: Angular 15, NX, PrimeNg Udemy- 10/10/2023.
- FullStack: Spring Boot Java 8 and Angular 9 TypeScript Udemy- 07/01/2023
- Angular y NodeJS in Production-Set up VPS Servers. Udemy- 05/16/2022
- Master JavaScript: Angular JQuery NodeJs. Udemy- 03/12/2022
- Master CSS: Responsive Design, Flexbox, Grid, Bootstrap Udemy- 12/09/2020